Cornelia Marschall Smith papers, Inclusive: 1915-2006, undated, Bulk: 1960-1988, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Subject Files, 1929-1994, undated; 4
  - Lowery, Michael, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - M.L.A. Convention, 1978 December (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Marschalls: Addresses, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Marschall, Genealogischen Handbuche Des Adels, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Marschall, Wilhelm von Bieberstein: Biography by Irene M. King, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Marschall, Wolfgang: Letters From, 1979-1986 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Mauldin Materials, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - McReynolds, Jene, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - “Memoir of My Life,” by Cornelia Smith, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Memorial Contributions, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Metropolitan Opera Guild, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Meusebach Materials, 1987-1991, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Middle East Week: Baylor University, 1978 September 10-15 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Milton’s Paradise Lost Study Questions, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Moritt’s “The Third Kiss,” Lyric Book, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - MOrtra Board: central Texas Alumnae Chapter, Paid Membership, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - New Jersey-New York-Washington Trip, 1978 September (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - New York, 1981: Playbill—“Amadeus” (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - New York, 1981: Playbill—“Crimes of the Heart” (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - New York, 1981: Playbill—“The Dresser” (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - New York, 1981: Playbill—“The West Side Waltz” (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - New York, 1981: “The Seagull” (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Number of Men vs. Women in Public Office, 1972-1979 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Oerke, Andrew, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Opera—Ft. Worth, 1980s-1990s (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Opera—Santa Fe, N.M., 1986 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Orient, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Retirement: Dr. J.W. Ousley, 1986 March 17 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Request: Lula Pace Items for a Biography, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Presses: Trajectory (Irene Marschall King) University Presses, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Programs for School of Music and the Baylor Theatre, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Professorships, 1980-1988 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Poage (Bob), 1979, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Minnie Stevens Piper Foundation, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - The Physical Browning, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Installation, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Pape, Mrs. Nell: Honorary Degree—Baylor, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Publishers Recommended by Dr. Colimer (1 of 2), 1983-1987, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Publishers Recommended by Dr. Colimer (2 of 2), 1983-1987, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1986-1990 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Restaurants, 1978, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Herbert H. Reynolds, 1981-1988, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Robinson, H.L and J.B. Smith, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Schofield, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Scholarship Fund—Charles G. and Cornelia Marschall Smith, 1987, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Sculpture in Texas, 1986 April 15 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Shakespeare Festivals, 1986, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Shakespeare Festival at Winedale—James Ayers, 1985, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Portrait of Shelley, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Sierra Club, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Texas Women’s Hall of Fame, 1989-1994, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Trajectory, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Tri Beta, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Trudy Correspondence, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Waco Symphony Orchestra, Waco Civic Theater, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Wagner’s The Ring Seattle, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Wake Forest University (Paschel), 1983-1987 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Robert Penn Warren—Poet Laureate, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Wolf Trap, 1980 Summer (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Young Woman’s Christian Association, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Stetson University, 1986, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Strecker Museum—Archeologist, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - W.A. Tacker: Consider for Article in Baylor Line, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Waco Tribune Herald Articles, 1971-1989 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Gary Smith, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 25)